So far, crystalline silicon solar cells are dominant in the photovoltaic field due to their high efficiency, low selling price and process maturity.

Since room temperature (300 K) measurements of I–V and C–V characteristics alone cannot provide detailed information about the mechanisms responsible for the formation of barrier  at the interface of the MS and electrical properties of devices, additional insight is gained by characterising the diodes
over a wide temperature range (40–300 K). 

The analysis of  the current-voltage (I-V)  characteristic of  a solar cell is one of  the most important diagnostic methods that may be used  to characterize the solar cell.  The current-voltage  equation that models the solar cell by  an equivalent electrical circuit contains several parameters related to physical phenomena occurring in  the device.  Changes in the parameter values may  reveal  important information about  the effects of  environmental conditions (e.g. radiation  effects on space solar cells) or manufacturing processes on  the performance of  solar cell. 

initial iron concentration at or below 1013 cm3 has no observable influence on...

Beside well developed silicon PV which covers almost 90% of global market [1] the other technologies such as dye-sensitized [2] or thin film [3] solar cells are available.

Fig. 4 shows the  series resistance  over the explored temperature range. 

The contacts size was chosen to avoid edge effects

Metal-Semiconductor (M-S) contacts are found to be important research activity because the knowledge of barrier formation is still far from the complete despite the fact that they are work horse at many electronic applications  like surge protection,  high speed operation, microwave field effect transistors, radio frequency detectors, temperature sensors and solar cells etc. 

A low n is preferable, because that results in a more rectangular J–V curve

We have used two approaches to calculate the depletion region. The first approach is based 

The content of this paper is organized as follows. In Section II, we present the formalism and the numerical implementation for trap level extraction. The impact of electric field on semiconductor traps and on different trap configurations is presented in Section III. Section IV considers the impact on the oxide trap characteristics. The electric field impact on the emission rates of semiconductor and oxide traps is discussed in Section V. Finally, we conclude this paper in Section VI.

For photovoltaic (PV) applications, Si, particularly in single-crystalline and multi-crystalline wafer form, is still the most widely-used material for industry; therefore, understanding the material properties including bulk lifetimes and the quality of the surface passivation is a top priority for many PV module manufacturers.

This spectral dependence is, to some degree, the result...

The spectra are  shifted vertically for ease of viewing. The intensity of spectrum 3 was divided by 4. 

All wafers were characterised using a Sinton Instruments WCT-120 tool and analysed using the generalised technique.

Some wafers were also transformed into 50?50 mm2  solar cells by using an industrial standard process. Both surfaces were texturized by the anisotropic chemical attack developed by the KOH solution. The n+ emitter was formed by phosphorus diffusion. Then a SiN-H layer used as antireflection coating was deposited on the front surface by PECVD. The silver front and aluminum rear electrodes were deposited by screen printing before rapid annealing. 

Exemplary degradation curves are shown in Fig. 3.

However, a state C has not been described in the cited study.

Figure 2 depicts a...

A close agreement has been found

One  detector,  irradiated  with  6 x  10^11  n/cm^2  and stored  for  6 months  at  room  temperature,  was  studied  in more  detail  using  isochronal  annealing. 

Crystalline silicon (Si) solar cells have occupied an important place in the solar cell market and have been researched to achieve further reduction in costs and improvement in the conversion efficiency.

The data have been processed and analyzed  within the framework of the most generalized approach...

It is worth keeping this fact in mind when...

Fig. 5 displays themeasured TCs of the FF of the studied cells and that of record silicon cells together with a generic theoretical calculation (green line) and speciﬁc theoretical predictions based on experimental values for each cell (triangles). 

The discussion of the realistic values of the ideality factor is beyond the scope of this paper.

From the foregoing, it is concluded that...

These are labeled ‘‘DDTT’’ from now on.

...in a range three orders of magnitude below...

The increase in Joe being attributed to the increase in surface area...

One way of reducing the electron or hole concentration at the surface is by introducing an electric ﬁeld.

Once t is determined, the threading dislocation density (NTD) and the barrier height can be obtained from Eq. (5).

In the following analysis, Teff is considered approximately equal to 1, a true condition for quasi-ballistic devices.

A vacuum-tight dewar  was used to measure the current–voltage characteristic of our samples at either room temperature or be-
low.