The paper is devoted to the new method of the current mechanism determination and barrier height extraction. Authors are bringing into community the method, which is based on using of the differential slope of the reverse current-voltage characteristic. Conclusions and abstract reflect main results of the article. References are appropriate. The work could be interesting for JAP. I have minor comments:

1. The term "kT/q" in equations, located  in the last column of Table 1 (second, third and fourth rows)  must be replaced by "kT" (or "qΔφ, eV" must be replaced by "Δφ, V" in the first row ).

2.  At many real MS interfaces, the ideality factor is included in the description of the junction current. The greater-than-unity ideality factor (and bias dependence of a SBH) can be caused by not only image force and interface states but also thermionic field emission, generation-recombination, SBH inhomogeneity. The expected behavior of the differential slope of the I-V characteristics in the last cases would be interesting .

3. "V" must be replaced by "Vr" in the Eq.(4), Fig.3(c).

4. The reason for selection of illumination wave length (365 nm) should be discussed. 

5. Possibly, the semi-log scale is  more relevant for the Fig.3(b).

6. If the dependence on Fig.3(c) is described by the Eq.(6) then it is possible to determinate the Vbi and Nd values. So, the comparison of the extracted donor concentration and built-in voltage with known sample parameters can be important part of the experimental verification of the introduced method.

7. It is claimed (page 10, first and second paragraphs from the bottom) that "ideality factor ...in the present case is 1.12... The small deviation of the ideality factor from a value of unity indicates that the current flow by thermionic emission is disturbed by the effect of the voltage dependent image force potential".
However n=1.12 is too much for image force influence. In this case
n=1+0.25*(q^3 Nd / 8 Pi^2 (eo es Vbi)^3)^0.25
One can calculate, that for n=1.12 and silicon
Nd=1.1e27 (Vbi)^3  1/m^3.
Therefore semiconductor is degenerate, or diffusion potential is too small, or ideality factor value is not determined by image force. The last version is most probable. It is important to report some details about this situation in the text.

8. On my humble opinion, while referring on equation from table it is better to use (number) than raw and column.

9. Figure 4 (e) shows the barrier height alteration under illumination. On the one hand, quasi-Fermi level position can be calculated by eqs.(4) and (7). On the another hand, quasi-Fermi level position depend on nonequilibrium carrier concentration, which is determined by  illumination power. The comparison of results, which obtained by this different way, would be interesting. 

10.  Page 12, 3-rd paragraph from the top: "In the dark and at small illumination powers, ∆φo values were extracted by the 
equation of raw II, column IV in table 1 while at large illuminations, we used the equation of row I, column IV."
Which is rigorous criterion for every equation using (or separation of small and large illuminations)?

11. Page 13, 1-st paragraph from the top: "(see inset in Fig. 2 (b))" must be replaced by "(see inset in Fig. 6 (b)) "

12. Figure 7 presents zero bias barrier height. At such condition Vr equals to zero. Therefore expressions in row I and row III are equivalent. Why are results obtained from reverse and forward branches different?

13. The word "raw" (pages 12, 15) must be replaced by "row".





Strengths:
1. Interesting results.
2. Examination of the intermediate case, which is located between diffusion and diode theories.
3. Novel approximate solution.
4. The theoretical consideration of structure, which is closed to real case.

Weaknesses:
1. Not good English
2. The absence of calculation details.
3. The absence of testing of novel approximate solution.

