
The authors have provided answers to my comments. But I beg to differ with Reply "The reviewer is correct, but it requires solving the transcendent equation (6), which is difficult... " Not transcendent equation, only Δφ^4 vs Vr plot and linear fitting... And known Nd (how many?) should be compared with Nd, which is obtained from the slop.
And major revision leads to some comments.

1. In text: The technique  we propose does not require to resort to complicated graphical differentiation techniques..."

Comment. But α determination procedure demands just graphical differentiation


2. In text: However,  even an error in determination of the area or Θ by factor of 10 can vary the actual barrier height by only ~12 % due to the logarithmic term in equation (14)...

Comment. The transmission coefficient is defined by exp term usually and factor of 10 is not limit.


3.In text: The parameters of the maximum point  (αmax, Vmax and Imax) enable extraction of the ideality factor, total barrier height φbn and series resistance [22] which in the present case are 1.12, 0.65 eV and 0.89 Ω, respectively.

Comment. What for are these data presented? The next paragraph states that n value (1.12) is incorrect. 
I propose to keep results, which are shown on Fig.3(d) only.


4. Information
"the small deviation of the ideality factor from 1 can certainly be attributed to the influence of image force potential.."
is repeated twice in the last and last but one paragraphs on p.11.


5. In text: Fig. 4... (c) Image force potential extracted from experimental data...

Comment. Why does image force depend on illumination? The complete barier height variation is presented on Fig.4(c), is not it?


6. Conclusion about series resistance is not supported by manuscript data.

On my opinion, the paper can be accepted for publication and the litle minor revision is needed.






The paper can be accepted for publication. 


Reviewer #2 Evaluations: 
RECOMMENDATION: Publish as is 
Sufficient New Physics in an Applied Area: Yes 
Appropriate Length: Yes 
Well Organized and Clearly Written: Yes 
Good Title: Yes 
Good Abstract: Yes 
Clear Figures: Yes 
Adequate References: Yes 
TECHNICAL QUALITY RATING: Good 
PRESENTATION RATING: Good 

Reviewer #2 (Comments to the Author): 

Required modifications from the previous review have been done in this version. As a result, this paper can be published as is. 