

Ref: RPC_2018_612

Title: Low dose gamma induced effects on structural and electrical properties of ZnSe/n-Si heterojunction

Radiation Physics and Chemistry

Dear Dr. Olikh,

Thank you for reviewing the above-referenced paper.

The current version of this manuscript (which may not be the one you reviewed) has been rejected for publication.

Reviewer and Editor comments to the author can be found below.

I appreciate your time and effort in reviewing this paper and greatly value your assistance as a reviewer for Radiation Physics and Chemistry.

I hope you enjoyed using Scopus and that it helped you to review this article. If you have not yet activated or completed your 30-day full access to Scopus, you can still do so. You can start your 30-day access period at any time within 6 months of the date you accepted the invitation to review.

Kind regards,

Christopher Chantler

Editor-in-Chief

Editor and reviewer comments:

--Reviewer 1

  - The paper is about influence of gamma-rays on properties of semiconductor barrier structures. Authors are bringing into community the interesting

experimental results.  But physical reasons of results are not discussed enough. I have following comments.

1. Some disadvantages are in paper preparation:
i) terms d and δ (see eqs (1) and (4)) are not defined;
ii) word "anamaouls " (page 5) is uncorrect;
iii) "λ=1.5406" must be in place of "??=1.5406" on page 5;
iv) "a" on page 3 is equivalent to "aznse" on page 10.


2. Authors have to operate with references more carefully. I do not check up all references, but
i) [17] is absent both in Microelectronics Reliability and Scopus;
ii) [15-17] does not deal with correlation of the ideality factor value and barrier inhomogeneity (see page 10) really;
iii) [16] does not contain any information about lattice constant, crystallite size,  lattice strain, and dislocation densities (see page 5)
iv) The using own paper only in tunneling current discussion is not good way.


3. In my humble opinion:
i) the detailed information of conventional method of least squares as well as Cheung model (item 3.2.1 and 3.2.2) is not necessary;
ii) the Fig.4 would be better if it consisted of two parts: one containing the H-functions, the other one being the dV/d(lnI)-functions.

4. The dose dependencies of all extracted parameters are extremely non-monotonic! For instance dependencies of both barrier height and lattice

parameter have the minimum as well as the maximum. It can be connected with a complex physical phenomenon or a bad accurancy. Therefore
i) The accurancy must be discussed. At that paper version any information about accuracy is absent. By the way, the slope determination from 4 or

5 points (see Fig. 4) is far from high precision.
ii) The physical reasons of non-monotonic change must be discussed.

5. What kind of structure is under investigation?
If it is heterojunction then eq. (5) and both Cheung and Bennett methods are inapplicable.
If it is Schottky structure with thin semiconductor interfacial layer then the title must be changed and the applicability of eq.(5) must be discussed.

6. Why do not the authors use the same region in the Chung and Bennett methods?

7. Page 10:
"Therefore, the thermionic emission of electrons over the barrier and the space charge limited emission mechanisms are the competing transport
mechanisms over the entire voltage region. In addition to these, the tunneling and tunneling through the trap states could be also expected to take
place at lower forward voltages [16, 17]."
On the one hand, any proof of space charge limited current or tunneling current is not adduce.
On the other hand, if forward current consist of thermoemission current, space charge limited current, and tunneling current then the eq. (5) and
both Cheung and Bennett methods are inapplicable and the gamma-rays are possible to not influence barrier height.

-Reviewer 2

  -

The manuscript presents experimental work on the structural and electrical properties of ZnSe/n-Si heterojunction under gamma irradiation. Several questions need to be addressed.


1. Is the goal of the experimental research to use gamma irradiation to engineer the structural and electrical properties of ZnSe/n-Si heterojunction? Why is gamma irradiation used instead of other techniques? What are other techniques?

 

2. Is the study to find out physical properties of the heterojunction under gamma irradiation? What are the specific applications of ZnSe/n-Si heterojunction related to gamma irradiation? Solar cells used in space? If so, do you expect the gamma irradiation affects the energy conversion efficiency, reliability and other physical properties of the solar cells?

 

3. In the last paragraph in the introduction section, how is the potential applicability of ZnSe/n-Si barrier to magnetic tunnel junctions related to gamma irradiation?

 

4. Also in the last paragraph in the introduction section, it is said that gamma irradiation is quite a simple technique in modifying and understanding the fundamental behavior of thin film heterojunction properties. Why is gamma irradiation a simple technique compared with other approaches e.g. thermal annealing? The gamma irradiation approach requires great care of radiation safety and proper licenses in most countries (if not all).

 

5. In the XRD analysis section, about reflections of the ZnSe before and after gamma irradiation, there are quite obvious peaks (Fig. 1) after irradiation of 6kGy and 10 kGy but not in other three cases. What are the reasons behind? What would cause such an irregular trend or behaviour?

 

6. In Equations (1) to (4), what  q values are used in calculating especially crystallinity (D) and lattice strain (𝜀) at different doses including 2 kGy and 4 kGy?

 

7. In the I-V characteristics of ZnSe/n-Si heterostructures (Fig. 3), why is the un-irradiated heterojunction not displaying an obvious exponential behavior in the forward biased region? What is the expected turn-on voltage of such a heterojunction? What is the approximate junction area? Why is the significant reverse-biased current after 2 kGy gamma irradiation but later less severe with 8 kGy and 10 kGy?

 

8. What are the mechanisms that cause the change in the series resistance Rs in the heterojunction?

 

9. In section 3. 2. 2 Method of least squares, it mentions about the tunneling and tunneling through the trap states, are there any more details available explained by using the energy band diagrams?

 

10. What physical processes and how do they cause the change in the lattice constant (𝑎), crystallinity (D), lattice strain (𝜀), dislocation density (𝛿) and lattice mismatch (Δ) at different irradiation doses of nanometer film? How about the barrier height (ΦB) the ZnSe/n-Si heterojunction?

 

One final comment is that there are several typographic errors in the manuscript, including “where ?? = 1.5406 Å” and “anamaouls”.