The paper is about influence of gamma-rays on properties of semiconductor barrier structures. Authors are bringing into community the interesting experimental results.  But physical reasons of results are not discussed enought. The work could be a good article for Radiation Physics and Chemistry after minor revision. I have following comments.

1. Some disadvantages are in paper preparation:
i) terms d and δ (see eqs (1) and (4)) are not defined;
ii) word "anamaouls " (page 5) is uncorrect;
iii) "λ=1.5406" must be in place of "??=1.5406" on page 5;
iv) "a" on page 3 is equivalent to "aznse" on page 10.


2. Authors have to operate with references more carefully. I do not check up all references, but
i) [17] is absent both in Microelectronics Reliability and Scopus;
ii) [15-17] does not deal with correlation of the ideality factor value and barrier inhomogeneity (see page 10) really;
iii) [16] does not contain any information about lattice constant, crystallite size,  lattice strain, and dislocation densities (see page 5)
iv) The using own paper only in tunneling current discussion is not good way.


3. In my humble opinion:
i) the detailed information of conventional method of least squares as well as Cheung model (item 3.2.1 and 3.2.2) is not necessary;
ii) the Fig.4 would be better if it consisted of two parts: one containing the H-functions, the other one being the dV/d(lnI)-functions.

4. The dose dependencies of all extracted parameters are extremely non-monotonic! For instance dependencies of both barrier height and lattice parameter have the minimum as well as the maximum. It can be connected with a complex physical phenomenon or a bad accurancy. Therefore
i) The accurancy must be discussed. At that paper version any information about accuracy is absent. By the way, the slope determination from 4 or 5 points (see Fig. 4) is far from high precision.
ii) The physical reasons of non-monotonic change must be discussed.

5. What kind of structure is under investigation?
If it is heterojunction then eq. (5) and both Cheung and Bennett methods are inapplicable.
If it is Schottky structure with thin semiconductor interfacial layer then the title must be changed and the applicability of eq.(5) must be discussed.

6. Why do not the authors use the same region in the Chung and Bennett methods?

7. Page 10:
"Therefore, the thermionic emission of electrons over the barrier and the space charge limited emission mechanisms are the competing transport mechanisms over the entire voltage region. In addition to these, the tunneling and tunneling through the trap states could be also expected to take place at lower forward voltages [16, 17]."
On the one hand, any proof of space charge limited current or tunneling current is not adduce.
On the other hand, if forward current consist of thermoemission current, space charge limited current, and tunneling current then the eq. (5) and both Cheung and Bennett methods are inapplicable and the gamma-rays are possible to not influence barrier height.






Strengths:

Weaknesses:

The main weakness is absence of appropriate discussion of experimental results.