The paper is about the simulation of a polymer solar cell with various layers.
The authors conducted simple modeling, and the results were not discussed enough. I recommend rejecting the manuscript.
I have the following comments.

1. The manuscript's title suggests an "investigation of the effect of metal plasmonics", but the study does not provide any information on the modeling of plasmonic effects. Additionally, the SCAPS software does not account for the phenomenon of local surface plasmon resonance. Instead, the study only involves modeling J-V curves for systems with the ZnS layer, which the authors associate with nanoparticles in some way. It is unclear absolutely how the modeling process took into account the effects, which are described in Section II.

2. The authors correlate changes in the parameters of the solar cell (pages 4, 7, and Conclusion) with changes in the shunt resistances and series resistances. Although determining these resistances from the current-voltage characteristics is a standard procedure, the study did not perform it. Therefore, the statement about the influence of resistance appears unsubstantiated.

3. The authors mention real structures several times (on page 2 and in the Acknowledgments for SEM and TEM measurements). However, the study does not present any experimental results for these real structures, specifically with SEM and TEM. Including such results could have potentially confirmed the study's conclusions.

4.The purpose of Section IV.B is unclear as it provides general information and several dependencies obtained through SCAPS. The determination of the built-in potential was performed for only one thickness of the absorber layer, and a narrow range of the voltage-capacitance dependence was chosen. It is unclear why the dependence is nonlinear for different voltage ranges, and the magnitude of the built-in potential is not compared to any other value or literature data.

5.All three highlights make the same claim.
This indicates that even the authors themselves feel that the results of their work are not very diverse.

6. According to pages 6 and 7, ZnS has an impact on both absorption and charge collection. However, no explanation or discussion is given regarding how this effect arises. 

The study's findings consist of SCAPS-calculated dependencies (J-V, C-V EQE-wavelength) for structures with differing absorber layer thicknesses. Most of the text covers familiar material or the dependencies themselves without proper analysis ("what you vising what you get"). 

Additionally, the paper suffers from poor preparation. Namely,

7. There is no information about other layers of the solar cell besides P3HT:PCBM and ZnS. Table I is extremely inconvenient.

8.Figure 1b is not relevant to the study - the simulated solar cell does not include a silicon layer with embedded metal nanoparticles.

9.The scale for most curves in Figure 4 is chosen extremely poorly.

10. The captions for Figures 5 and 10 are incorrect.

11. There is no information on what distinguishes the curves in Figure 5.

12.The data in Table II duplicate Figure 4. The same applies to Table III and Figure 11.

13.On page 3, it is stated that "These results agree with the experimental results found in reference [26]." However, the similarity to the results of [26] is subjective.

14. On page 4, it is stated that "The maximum power conversion efficiency was found at an absorber layer thickness 200nm as shown in Figure 3." However, this is not visible in Figure 3.

15. Comparison with the results of [28] is not relevant, as paper [28] does not relate to organic solar cells.

16. The expected advantages of using ZnS nanoparticles compared to other materials are not specified.

17. On page 6, it is stated that "This performance is much better than that of Pristine." The difference is only 0.6%.

18. On page 6, it is stated that "It has been observed in many experiments that the large weight of NPs results in poor-performing devices," but corresponding references to these results are not provided.

19. On page 6, it is stated that "From Figure 5, the 3 nm has the highest maximum power compared to other curves (9 nm to 12 nm)." However, Figure 5 does not relate to structures with different ZnS thicknesses.

20. On pages 6-7, it is stated that "Increasing the concentration of nanoparticles increases the defects in a device material. The defects can poorly affect the photon absorption by the device material." However, these claims are not self-evident. For example, defects often cause additional light absorption and the appearance of additional spectral bands.

21. In the Conclusion, it is stated that "The device program works under room temperatures, and allows single or batch calculations at once." However, SCAPS allows calculations to be performed not only at room temperature. Additionally, this information, in my opinion, should not be included in the conclusions of the work.

22. The manuscript requires editing, for instance, it often includes capital letters in the middle of sentences and lowercase letters after periods.



Strengths:
-------

Weaknesses:

The main weakness is absence of interesting results.
There is no evidence that specifically plasmonic effects were modeled.



1. The manuscript title states about "investigation of the effect of metal plasmonic".
Проте в роботі не наведено ніякої інформації щодо моделювання  плазмонних ефектів. 
SCAPS software не передбачає врахування phenomenon of local surface plasmon resonance.
Фактично, в роботі проведено моделювання J-V кривих для систем в шаром ZnS,
які автори чомусь насивають наночастинками.
Незрозуміло, яким чином ефекти, описані в розділі ІІ, враховані під час моделювання.

2. Автори пов'язують зміни параметрів сонячного елементу (page 4, 7, Conclusion) зі змінами шунтуючого та послідовного опорів.
Визначення цих опорів з вольт-амперних характеристик є стандартною процедурою, проте в роботі 
це не було зроблено. Тому твердження про впив опорів виглядає голослівним,

3.Автори декілька разів згадують про реальні структури (page 2 and Acknowledgments for SEM and TEM measurements).
Проте ніяких результатів експериментів з реальними структурами не наведено, а вони могли б підтвердити висновки роботи.

4. Незрозуміле призначення Розділу ІV.B. Він містить загальну інформацію та декілька залежностей, отриманих за допомогою SCAPS.
Визначення вбудованого потенціалу проведено лише для однієї товщини absorber layer, при цьому вибрано лише окрему ділянку вольт-фарадної залежності.
Чому для інших діапазонів напруги залежність нелінійна не пояснено, величина вбкдованого потенціалу ні з чим не порівняна.

5. Всі 3 highlights стверджують одне й те саме.

6. Стверджується (page 6 and 7), що ZnS influenced both absorption and collection of charges, проте як саме це відбувається не пояснюється та не обговорюється.

Фактично, результати цієї роботи - це залежності, розраховані за допомогою SCAPS для структур з різними товщинами absorber layer.
Текстові дані стосуються або загальновідомих речей (розділ ІІ, значні частини розділів III та IV.B), або простого опису залежностей (what you vising what you get).

Крім того, робота погано підготовлена. А саме

7. Не має жодної інформації про інші шари сонячного елементу, окрім P3HT:PCBM та ZnS. Табл.І надзвичайно незручна.

8.Рис.1b не стосується роботи - в симулюваному сонячному елементі не передбачено шару кремнію з вкрапленням металевих наночастинок.

9. Масштаб для більшості кривих на рис.4 вибрано надзвичайно невдало.

10. Підписи до рис.5 та 10 неправильні.

11. Відсутня інформація щодо того, чим відрізняються криві на Рис.5.

12. Дані табл.ІІ дублюють рис.4. Те саме стосується табл.ІІІ та рис.11.

13. It is stated at page 3 "These results agree with the the
experimental results found in reference [26]".
Проте подібність з результатами роботи [26] дуже відносна.

14.It is stated at page 4 "The maximum power conversion efficiency was found at
an absorber layer thickness 200nm as shown in Figure 3."
Проте на рис.3 цього не видно.

15.Порівняння з результатами роботи [28] не доречне, так як вона не стосується органічних сонячних елементів.

16. Не вказані очікувані переваги від використання саме ZnS наночастинок порівняно з іншими матеріалами.

17. It is stated at page 6 "This performance is much better than that of Pristine". Відмінність складає лише 0,6%.

18. It is stated at page 6 "It has been observed in many experiment, that the large weight of Nps result in poor performing devices." Проте посилання на відповідні результати відсутні.   

19. It is stated at page 6 "From Figure5 the 3 nm, has the highest maximum power compared to other curves(9 nm to 12 nm)."
   Проте рис.5 не стосується структур з різними товщинами ZnS.
  
20. It is stated at page 6-7 "Increasing the concentration of Nanoparticles increases the defects in a device material.The defects can poorly affect the photon absorption
by device material." Проте ці твердження не очевидні. Наприклад, саме дефекти нерідко спричинюю додаткове поглинання світла і появу додаткових смуг у спектрах.

21. at Conclusion "The device programme works under room temperatures, allows
single or batch calculations at once." SCAPS дозволяє проводити розрахунки  не лише при кімнатних температурах. І ця інформація, на мій погляд,
не може стосуватися висновків роботи.

22. Рукопис вимагає редагування, наприклад в ньому нерідко зустрічається велика літера посередині речення та мала літера після крапки.  




Strengths:

Weaknesses:

The main weakness is absence of interesting results.
Відсутні підтвердження, що моделювалися саме плазмонні ефекти.
