The paper is devoted to silicon photodetectors. Article subject is very interesting and impotent. To my regret the manuscript looks raw and crude.
So, 

1.Abstract does not agree with the manuscript content. For example, abstract says about "mechanism of current transport" whereas any word, which is devoted to current transport mechanism, does not preset in the text. Moreover   abstract unsoundly states that "It is shown that the two barrier structures can greatly improve the characteristics of conventional photoelectric detectors".
Finally, there are numerous repetitions in my version of manuscript .

2. Data, which are concerning influence of annealing temperature on structure properties, are absent. Therefore, conclusion about role of A-centers is not well-grounded. For example, "Isochronous (30 min.) annealing of radiation defects was carried out in the range of temperatures of Ta = 200-450 K." cannot be a reason of A-center annealing (~600 K). At 200 C (470 K) the boron-oxygen centers, which are responsible for LID, are annealed. Besides, at 300-350 C the E-centers are annealed too.

3. References represent papers of single author only. Can it really be true that another people do not investigate silicon photodetectors?

4. The purpose of Fig.1 is obscure.

5. How do equations, which are located in introduction ('"optical properties of films") deal with the experimental results?

6. The structure geometry is unclear. How was structure illuminated? How were I-V characteristics measured?

7. Data of Fig.2 are unmatched with data of Fig.3.

8. None of the figure number in the text does not agree with real number (one exception -- Fig.1). For example, two Fig.7 are present.

9. Caption of Fig.7 (second) and X-axis title are badly coordinated with each other. Why are these dependencies non-monotonic?

10.The physical reasons of influence on spectral characteristics of bias as well as irradiation and annealing are undiscussed.

11. Page 4, 3-rd paragraph from the top: "I showed that primary radiation defects (RD) in p-Si crystals at 300 K are loaded positively." In what way?

12. Page 4, 4-th paragraph from the top: "Annealing of diodes leads to decrease in recombination currents." 
At the same time the Figure 5 caption : "Annealing results are insignificant".

13. What are electron transitions  responsible for photoluminescence of silicon, which is illustrated by Fig.7 (first)?

14. Many abbreviations and symbols are not clarified.

15.The axis title on Fig.3 and Fig 6 is not correct.

16. What is wavelength used in Fig.4?

17. Not good English.

On my opinion, the major revision is needed.

