The paper is about theoretical study of ultrasound insertion in the low impedance media through steel tank. Authors are bringing into community the method, which is based on using of tone-burst signal. The work is systematic. References are appropriate. The work could be a good article for Ultrasonics. I have minor comments:

1. On my opinion, Continuous Wave (CW) must be introduced at the beginning.

2. Fig.3 relates to the transmission coefficient of steel plate only, is not it? It is not evident from the caption.

3. In the practical case, the measurements must be done at different temperatures. Some discussion about AETC temperature dependence would be interesting. 

4. Figures 4 and 5 are not good in the gray scale case.

5. Page 8, 2-nd row from the top: "in the inset figure of Fig.4b". The inset is absent on the Figure 4b.

6. How does amplitude of tone burst change  from one cycle to another? How does the amplitude change law affect on an ultrasound tunneling. It is necessary to give some detail on this topic.

7. Conclusion, first sentence: " An ultrasound tunneling method was analyzed and used to detect the level of different media in a closed steel tank". But any discussion about level is absent in the paper. What does word "level" mean?
For the configuration, which is shown on Fig.1, the location of water surface with regard to transducer can be determined only. But such binary information ("above" or "below")  can be obtained by using CW too. Namely, if received voltage equals to zero, then air is located near transducer. And water is located near transducer in the opposite case. Therefore the advantage of the tone-burst signal using is not evident.

8. 2-nd highlights does not reflect main results of the article.

9. Mention of the Comsol software would look well in the Setup, not in the Conclusion.






Strengths:
1. Interesting results.
2. Examination of the intermediate case, which is located between diffusion and diode theories.
3. Novel approximate solution.
4. The theoretical consideration of structure, which is closed to real case.

Weaknesses:
1. Not good English
2. The absence of calculation details.
3. The absence of testing of novel approximate solution.

